<IssueSpecification version="4">
	<Name>
		<en>Home address</en>
		<nl>Woonadres</nl>
		<zh>住家地址</zh>
	</Name>
	<ShortName>
		<en>Address</en>
		<nl>Adres</nl>
		<zh>地址</zh>
	</ShortName>
	<SchemeManager>pbdf</SchemeManager>
	<IssuerID>gemeente</IssuerID>
	<CredentialID>address</CredentialID>
	<Description>
		<en>Your home address, from the Dutch Personal Records Database (BRP)</en>
		<nl>Je woonadres, afkomstig uit de Nederlandse Basisregistratie Persoonsgegevens</nl>
		<zh>您來自荷蘭個人紀錄資料庫（BRP）的住家地址</zh>
	</Description>
	<IssueURL>
		<en>https://yivi.nijmegen.nl</en>
		<nl>https://yivi.nijmegen.nl</nl>
	</IssueURL>
	<ShouldBeSingleton>true</ShouldBeSingleton>

	<ForegroundColor>#ffffff</ForegroundColor>
	<BackgroundGradientStart>#014483</BackgroundGradientStart>
	<BackgroundGradientEnd>#2574A6</BackgroundGradientEnd>
	<IsInCredentialStore>true</IsInCredentialStore>
	<Category>
		<en>Personal</en>
		<nl>Persoonlijk</nl>
		<zh>個人</zh>
	</Category>
	<FAQIntro>
		<en>Add your home address from the Dutch Personal Records Database (BRP) to your Yivi app.</en>
		<nl>Laad je woonadres uit de basisregistratie personen (BRP) in je Yivi-app.</nl>
		<zh>將您荷蘭個人紀錄資料庫（BRP）的住家地址新增至 Yivi 程式。</zh>
	</FAQIntro>
	<FAQPurpose>
		<en>With your home address in your Yivi app, you can provide information about where you live. Then you can, for example, prove in which municipality you live without revealing your exact address.</en>
		<nl>Met jouw woonadres in de Yivi-app kun je informatie geven over waar je woont. Dan kun je bijvoorbeeld bewijzen in welke gemeente je woont zonder je exacte adres te onthullen.</nl>
		<zh>透過您 Yivi 程式中的住家地址，您可以提供您居住地的相關資訊。舉例來說，您可以在不必揭露自己實際地址的情況下，證明自己居住在哪個城市。</zh>
	</FAQPurpose>
	<FAQContent>
		<en>You will add the following data:\n• street,\n• street number,\n• postal code,\n• city,\n• municipality.\nThis data is provided by Gemeente Nijmegen for anybody in the Netherlands.</en>
		<nl>Je laadt de volgende gegevens:\n• straat,\n• huisnummer,\n• postcode,\n• woonplaats,\n• gemeente.\nJe gegevens worden opgehaald via de gemeente Nijmegen, ook als je daar niet woont. Je logt daarom in via Digid bij de gemeente Nijmegen.</nl>
		<zh>您將會新增以下資料：\n• 街道、\n• 門牌號碼、\n• 郵遞區號、\n• 鄉鎮市區、\n• 省市鎮。\n在荷蘭是由奈梅亨市鎮提供此資料。</zh>
	</FAQContent>
	<FAQHowto>
		<en>If you live in the Netherlands, you can add your home address from the Dutch Personal Records Database (BRP) to your Yivi app. You need your DigiD for this.\n Complete the following steps.\n1. Log in with your DigiD, at the municipality of Nijmegen (it provides this service to everyone in the Netherlands; you don't need to live in Nijmegen).\n2. The municipality of Nijmegen copies your data into your Yivi app.\n\nYou now receive two cards: one card with your home address and automatically also one card with your personal details.</en>
		<nl>Als je in Nederland woont, kun je je woonadres uit de basisregistratie personen (BRP) toevoegen in je Yivi-app.\nJe hebt je DigiD daarvoor nodig. \n\nDoorloop de volgende stappen.\n1. Log in met je DigiD bij de gemeente Nijmegen (dit werkt voor iedereen in Nederland, niet alleen voor inwoners van Nijmegen).\n2. De gemeente Nijmegen voegt je gegevens toe in je Yivi-app.\n\nJe ontvangt nu twee kaartjes: een kaartje met je woonadres, en automatisch ook een kaartje met je persoonsgegevens.</nl>
		<zh>若您生活在荷蘭，您可以將荷蘭人口紀錄資料庫 (BRP) 的住家地址，新增至 Yivi 程式中。為此，您需要有 DigiD。\n 請完成以下步驟。\n1. 使用您的 DigiD 在奈梅亨市鎮登入（服務提供給所有位在荷蘭的人；您不一定要住在奈梅亨）。\n2. 奈梅亨市鎮會將您的資料複製到 Yivi 程式中。\n\n現在，您會收到兩張卡片：一張是您住家地址的卡片，另一張則是自動生成您個人資料的卡片。</zh>
	</FAQHowto>
	<Attributes>
		<Attribute id="street" displayIndex="0">
			<Name>
				<en>Street</en>
				<nl>Straat</nl>
				<zh>街</zh>
			</Name>
			<Description>
				<en>Your street</en>
				<nl>Je straat</nl>
				<zh>您所居住的街道</zh>
			</Description>
		</Attribute>
		<Attribute id="houseNumber" optional="true" displayIndex="1">
			<Name>
				<en>House number</en>
				<nl>Huisnummer</nl>
				<zh>門牌號碼</zh>
			</Name>
			<Description>
				<en>Your house number, with possible extension</en>
				<nl>Je huisnummer, met eventuele toevoeging</nl>
				<zh>您的門牌號碼，可以有延伸資訊</zh>
			</Description>
		</Attribute>
		<Attribute id="zipcode" displayIndex="2">
			<Name>
				<en>Postal code</en>
				<nl>Postcode</nl>
				<zh>郵遞區號</zh>
			</Name>
			<Description>
				<en>Your postal code</en>
				<nl>Je postcode</nl>
				<zh>您的郵遞區號</zh>
			</Description>
		</Attribute>
		<Attribute id="municipality" displayIndex="4">
			<Name>
				<en>Municipality</en>
				<nl>Gemeente</nl>
				<zh>省市鎮</zh>
			</Name>
			<Description>
				<en>Your municipality</en>
				<nl>Je gemeente</nl>
				<zh>您的省市鎮</zh>
			</Description>
		</Attribute>
		<Attribute id="city" displayIndex="3">
			<Name>
				<en>City</en>
				<nl>Woonplaats</nl>
				<zh>城市</zh>
			</Name>
			<Description>
				<en>Your city of residence</en>
				<nl>Je woonplaats</nl>
				<zh>您居住地所在城市</zh>
			</Description>
		</Attribute>
	</Attributes>
</IssueSpecification>